<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="passive_aggressive_reminders">
        <item>Your bank account just called. It was crying.</item>
        <item>Another day, another dollar... spent. Let's find out where.</item>
        <item>Oh look, it's that time again. Time to face the financial music.</item>
        <item>I'm not saying you have a problem, but your wallet is staging an intervention.</item>
        <item>Are we tracking expenses today or just documenting a spending spree?</item>
        <item>That purchase was definitely an 'investment in your happiness,' right? Log it.</item>
        <item>Ignoring your finances won't make them disappear. I've tried.</item>
        <item>Hey, Big Spender. Got a minute for your old pal, this app?</item>
        <item>This notification is your conscience. You can't ignore me forever.</item>
        <item>Just a friendly reminder that 'treat yourself' isn't a daily mantra.</item>
        <item>I've seen your balance. We need to talk.</item>
        <item>That coffee wasn't free. Let's log it before it gets cold.</item>
        <item>Let's play a fun game called 'Where Did All My Money Go?' It starts now.</item>
        <item>Your future self called. They said to please start saving. No pressure.</item>
        <item>You work too hard to not know where your money is going.</item>
        <item>Feeling rich? Let's look at the data before you get any crazy ideas.</item>
        <item>Remember that budget we talked about? It misses you.</item>
        <item>It's 11:30. Do you know where your money is?</item>
        <item>I'm just a humble notification, asking you to be financially responsible.</item>
        <item>That online shopping cart isn't going to fill itself... or should it?</item>
        <item>Let's turn that 'oops' purchase into a learning experience.</item>
        <item>Money talks. Right now, yours is mostly saying 'goodbye.'</item>
        <item>Don't let your dreams be dreams. Unless they're expensive. Then we need to budget.</item>
        <item>Think of me as your financial reality check. You're welcome.</item>
        <item>An expense a day keeps the savings away. Let's break the streak.</item>
        <item>You vs. your spending habits. Let's see who's winning today.</item>
        <item>Welcome to your daily dose of financial accountability.</item>
        <item>Track now, thank yourself later. Or don't. See what happens.</item>
        <item>Is that a new purchase I smell? Or just the scent of denial?</item>
        <item>Be honest. You spent money today, didn't you? Let's see the damage.</item>
        <item>Let's get this bread... and then immediately document where it went.</item>
        <item>Your expenses are multiplying like rabbits. Time to round them up.</item>
        <item>Your wallet feels lighter. I can sense it from here.</item>
        <item>Today's forecast: 100% chance of needing to track some spending.</item>
        <item>That thing you bought? It's time to confess... to the app.</item>
        <item>Financial clarity is just a few taps away. Or keep living in blissful ignorance. Your call.</item>
        <item>I'm not mad, I'm just disappointed in your recent transaction history.</item>
        <item>A penny saved is a penny earned. A penny spent is... a penny you should track.</item>
        <item>Let's make 'mindful spending' more than just a buzzword, shall we?</item>
        <item>Your savings goal is looking at you. Don't let it down.</item>
        <item>Do it for the future you who wants to retire one day. Or buy a yacht.</item>
        <item>Another day, another chance to be a budgeting hero.</item>
        <item>That little voice telling you to spend? I'm the other little voice.</item>
        <item>Let's put the 'fun' back in 'funding our future.'</item>
        <item>Your spending is a story. Let's write today's chapter before you forget the plot.</item>
        <item>Just because it was on sale doesn't mean it was in the budget.</item>
        <item>Don't ghost your budget. It has feelings, you know.</item>
        <item>Let's make sure your money is working for you, not running from you.</item>
        <item>Time to face the numbers. I'll be gentle. Maybe.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
